A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - Real Estate, 1982-1986; 24; 20.49 Cubic Feet 49 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes
    - Pocantico Hills, 6
      - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Negotiations (Box 574, Folder 4-5)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Partition-Closing (Box 575, Folder 1-3)
      - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Bohlinger, 1984-1986 (Box 575, Folder 4)
      - Pocantico Hills - Planning (Box 576, Folder 1-2)
      - Pocantico Hills - Playhouse (Box 576, Folder 3-4)
      - Pocantico Hills - Frye - Pocantico Development - Frank Cross, 1984 August 2 (Box 577, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Historic Area (Box 577, Folder 2-4)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Institute (Proposed) (Box 577, Folder 5)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Village Master Plan, Sasaki Associates-Frye, 1984 August 2 (Box 577, Folder 6)
      - Pocantico Hills - President and Mrs. Ronald Reagan (Box 577, Folder 7)
      - Pocantico Hills - Background Material Proposed by Nat. Trust, P.R. Strategy, Briefing Paper, Nat. Trust Newsletter, 1979-1985 (Box 578, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Press Relase - Study George H. Bohlinger, 1984 July 9-12 (Box 578, Folder 2)
      - Pocantico Hills - National Trust Terms of Agreement, 1983 August 10 (Box 578, Folder 3)
      - Pocantico Hills - Press Release - National Trust-State Park, 1983 September 16 (Box 578, Folder 4)
      - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit Newsclip, 1979-1984 (Box 578, Folder 5-9)
      - Pocantico Hills - Press Release - State Park 3rd Meeting, 1982 September 29-30 (Box 578, Folder 10)
      - Pocantico Hills - Press Release - State Park Second Meeting, 1982 September 9 (Box 578, Folder 11)
      - Pocantico Hills - Press Briefings Proposed State Park, 1982 July 20 (Box 578, Folder 12)
      - Pocantico Hills - Partition and Public Hearings, 1983 March 1-14 (Box 578, Folder 13)
      - Pocantico Hills - Partition and Hearings, 1983 July 1 (Box 578, Folder 14)
      - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit Newsclip, 1983 (Box 579, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Sasaki-Maurice Freedman Paper - Westchester Speech, 1983 February 25 (Box 579, Folder 2)
      - Pocantico Hills - Press Release - State Park First Meeting, 1982 July 28 (Box 579, Folder 3)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Tax Situation, 1980-1984 (Box 579, Folder 4)
      - Pocantico Hills - Background Material, Press Conference, Press Releases, Principals Remarks, 1983 December 21 (Box 580, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Public Meeting, 1982 September 17 (Box 580, Folder 2)
      - Pocantico Hills - LSR Remarks, PIPC-Rock Lookout Plaque Dedication, 1981 October 24 (Box 580, Folder 3)
      - Pocantico Hills - PIPC Press Release - Fort Lee Palisades Park, 1976 (Box 580, Folder 4)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Houses (Box 580, Folder 5)
      - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Hills Community and Public Relations (Box 580, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc.-Rockefeller Group, 7
      - Rockefeller Center, Inc.-Rockefeller Group (Box 580, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller Center, Inc.-Rockefeller Group - General, 1980-1983 (Box 583, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Center, Inc.-Rockefeller Group - A-Z (Box 583, Folder 2-3)
      - Annual Review (Box 583, Folder 4)
      - Real Estate Development Committee (Box 584, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors (Box 584, Folder 2)
      - Clippings (Box 586, Folder 1)
      - Contributions (Box 586, Folder 2)
      - Cushman and Wakefield (Box 584, Folder 3)
      - Finances (Box 584, Folder 4-5)
      - Minutes-Meetings (Box 584, Folder 6)
      - Long Range Strategic Plan (Box 585, Folder 1)
      - 1934 Trust, 1984 (Box 585, Folder 2)
      - Printed Material (Tie Magazine and Centerscope) (Box 586, Folder 3-4)
      - Outlet Company (Box 585, Folder 3)
      - RCTV (Box 586, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller Center - A-Z (Box 587, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Center - Anzac Garden (and Dayo) (Box 587, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Center - Christmas Tree (Box 587, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller Center - 50th Anniversary (Box 587, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller Center - Historic Landmark (Box 587, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller Group - Rockefeller Center - Prudential Insurance Company (Box 587, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller Center - History (Box 588, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Center - Radio City Music Hall (Box 588, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Center - Rivera, Diego (Box 588, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller Center - Rockefeller Center Luncheon Club (Box 588, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller Development Group, Inc. - REIT (Box 589, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Center - Rockefeller Center Development Corp. - A-Z (Box 585, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller Center - Rockefeller Center Development Corp. - International Trade Center-New Jersey Foreign Trade Zone (Box 585, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller Center - Rockefeller Center Development Committee - Minutes-Meetings (Box 589, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller Center - Rockefeller Center Properties (Box 589, Folder 3-4, Box 590, Folder 1, Box 591, Box 592)
      - Rockefeller Center - Voell, Richard A (Box 592, Folder 2)
      - Wall Street Journal (Box 593, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts, 8
      - Rockresorts - A-G (Box 593, Folder 2-5)
      - Rockresorts - H-Z (Box 594, Folder 1-3)
      - The Boulders (Box 594, Folder 4, Box 595, Folder 1-4)
      - Caneel Bay, Inc. - A-Z (Box 595, Folder 5)
      - Dorado Beach (Box 596, Folder 1)
      - Finances (Box 598, Folder 1)
      - Heidrick and Struggles (Box 598, Folder 2)
      - La Belle Creole (Box 592, Folder 3)
      - Little Dix Bay - General (Box 596, Folder 2)
      - Little Dix Bay - A-Z (Box 596, Folder 3-5)
      - Little Dix Bay - Photo Album (Box 597, Folder 1-2)
      - Little Dix Bay - Bulletin (Box 597, Folder 3-4)
      - Little Dix Bay - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 598, Folder 3-4)
      - Little Dix Bay - Printed Material (Box 599, Folder 1)
      - Little Dix Bay - Stone, Edward D. Jr and Associates (Box 599, Folder 2)
      - Landauer Associates (Box 599, Folder 3)
      - Minutes-Meetings (Box 599, Folder 4, Box 600, Folder 1)
      - Mt. Tom (Box 600, Folder 2)
      - Planning (Strategic Planning), 1974-1985 (Box 600, Folder 3-5)
      - Publicity (Box 601, Folder 1)
      - Property Maps (Box 601, Folder 2)
      - Printed Material (Box 601, Folder 3)
      - Sale (Box 601, Folder 4)
      - Sale - CSX (Box 601, Folder 5, Box 602, Folder 1-3, Box 603, Folder 1)
      - Suicide Six (Box 603, Folder 2)
      - Victoria International Corporation (Box 603, Folder 3)
      - Victoria International Corporation - Morning Star of Harts Cove, LTD (Box 604, Folder 1)
    - Offers, 9
      - Offers - A-Z (Box 605, Folder 3-7)
  - Religion, 1982-1986; 25; 6.46 Cubic Feet 17 letter document boxes
    - Religion - A-Z, 1
      - Religion - A-E (Box 606, Folder 1-4)
      - Religion - F-M (Box 607, Folder 1-5)
      - Religion - N-S (Box 608, Folder 1-3)
      - Religion - S-Z (Box 609, Folder 1-3)
      - A Christian Ministry in National Parks (Box 609, Folder 4)
      - A Christian Ministry in National Parks - Printed Material (Box 609, Folder 5)
      - Agape Foundation (Box 609, Folder 6)
      - American Friends Service Committee (Box 610, Folder 1-2)
      - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (Box 610, Folder 3-4)
      - Appeal of Conscience Foundation (Box 611, Folder 1-2)
      - Bread for the World Educational Fund (Box 611, Folder 3)
      - Cardinal Cooke Guild (Box 611, Folder 4)
      - Center for Theological Inquiry (Box 611, Folder 5)
      - Christic Institute (Box 612, Folder 1-2)
      - Christic Institute-South (Box 612, Folder 3)
      - Citizens Freedom Foundation, Inc. (Box 612, Folder 4)
      - Council on Religion and International Affairs (Box 613, Folder 1)
      - Dharma Sangha (Box 613, Folder 2)
      - Friends of Creation Spirituality, Inc. (Box 613, Folder 3-4)
      - Fund for the Enhancement of the Human Spirit (Box 614, Folder 1)
      - Hospital Chaplaincy, Inc. (Box 614, Folder 2)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc. (Box 614, Folder 3)
      - Northern California Ecumenical Council (Box 615, Folder 1-2)
      - Riverdale Center of Religious Research (Box 614, Folder 4)
      - Seamen's Church Institute of New York and New Jersey (Box 614, Folder 5)
      - United Church of Christ (Box 615, Folder 3)
      - Zen Center, California, 1972-1986 (Box 615, Folder 4-5, Box 616, Folder 1)
      - Zen Studies Center, New York (Box 616, Folder 2)
      - Zen Center, San Francisco (Box 616, Folder 3)
    - Churches, 2
      - Churches - A-M (Box 616, Folder 4-7)
      - Churches - N-Z (Box 617, Folder 1-4)
      - American Church in Paris (Box 617, Folder 5)
      - Brick Presbyterian Church (Box 617, Folder 6)
      - Canterbury Cathedral, Canterbury, England, 1977-1985 (Box 618, Folder 1)
      - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine (Box 618, Folder 2-4)
      - The Church of St. Luke in the Fields (Box 618, Folder 5)
      - Claveria United Church, 1975-1976 (Box 618, Folder 6)
      - Council of Churches in the City of New York (Box 619, Folder 1)
      - First Congregational Church, Woodstock, VT, 1977-1983 (Box 619, Folder 2)
      - Judson Church, Rangoon, Burma (Box 619, Folder 3)
      - National Council of Churches of Christ in the United States of America (Box 619, Folder 4)
      - National Council of Churches of Christ in the United States of America - Division of Church and Society (Box 619, Folder 5)
      - Riverside Church (Box 620, Folder 1-2)
      - Riverside Church - Contributions (Box 620, Folder 3)
      - St. Francis Friends of the Poor (Box 620, Folder 4)
      - St, John's Church, Jackson, WY (Box 620, Folder 5)
      - St. Patrick's Cathedral (Box 621, Folder 1)
      - United Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 621, Folder 2)
      - United Church of Pocantico Hills - Contributions (Box 621, Folder 3)
      - United Church of Pocantico Hills - Printed Matter (Box 621, Folder 4)
    - Missions, 3
      - Missions - A-Z (Box 621, Folder 5)
      - New York City Mission Society (Box 622, Folder 1-2)
      - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc. (Box 622, Folder 3-4)
      - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc. - Printed Material (Box 622, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1982-1986; 26; 57.72 Cubic Feet 140 letter document boxes, 8 legal document boxes, 1 wide letter document box, and 1 oversize box
    - Rockefeller Family - General, 1
      - Rockefeller Family - A-Z (Box 623, Folder 1)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. (Box 623, Folder 2)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch - A-Z (Box 623, Folder 3-4)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Annual Report (Box 623, Folder 5)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch - Clippings (Box 624, Folder 1)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Finances (Box 624, Folder 2)
      - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Minutes-Meetings (Box 624, Folder 3)
      - Awards (Box 624, Folder 4)
      - Awards - Westchester Tricentennial Commission (Box 624, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Party (Box 625, Folder 1)
      - Cousins (Box 625, Folder 2-3)
      - Cousins - Articles (Box 625, Folder 4)
      - The Fifth Generation (Box 626, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Living Rockefeller family
      - Rockefeller Family Reunion (Box 626, Folder 2)
      - Trusts (Box 626, Folder 3, Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Abby Rockefeller Mauze (and family), 2
      - Mauze, Abby Rockefeller (Box 633, Folder 1)
      - Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust - General (Box 633, Folder 2)
      - Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust - General - Grants - A-Z (Box 633, Folder 3-5)
      - O'Neill, Abby (Gail) (Box 635, Folder 3)
      - O'Neill, David M. (Box 635, Folder 4)
      - O'Neill, George Doer and Abby Milton (Box 635, Folder 5)
      - O'Neill, George Jr. (Box 635, Folder 6)
      - O'Neill, George Jr. - Works of Art, 1985 (Box 635, Folder 7)
      - O'Neill, Mr. and Mrs. Grover III (Box 636, Folder 1)
      - O'Neill, Peter (Box 636, Folder 2)
      - Simpson, Abby Rockefeller (Box 767, Folder 1-2)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton (Box 767, Folder 3)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton - Marilyn M. Simpson Charitable Income Trusts (Box 766, Folder 3)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton - Marilyn M. Simpson Charitable Income Trusts - A (Box 766, Folder 4)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton - Marilyn M. Simpson Charitable Income Trusts - B-H (Box 766, Folder 5)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton - Marilyn M. Simpson Charitable Income Trusts - I-S (Box 768, Folder 1-4)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton - Marilyn M. Simpson Charitable Income Trusts - T-Z (Box 769, Folder 1)
      - Simpson, Mr. and Mrs. William Kelly and Marilyn Milton - Marilyn M. Simpson Charitable Income Trusts - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA, School of Veterinary Medicine (Box 769, Folder 2)
      - Thorn, Laura (Laura S. O'Neill) (Box 767, Folder 6)
      - Thorn, Laura (Laura S. O'Neill) - Giving Program (Box 770, Folder 1-4)
      - Thorn, Laura (Laura S. O'Neill) - Giving Program - Payment Letters, 1981-1986 (Box 770, Folder 5-6)
      - Thorn, Laura (Laura S. O'Neill) - Giving Program - Correspondence, 1981-1987 (Box 771, Folder 1-2)
      - Thorn, Laura (Laura S. O'Neill) - Giving Program - Meetings-Funding Decisions (Box 771, Folder 3)
    - David Rockefeller (and family), 3
      - Rockefeller, David - A (Box 639, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, David - B (Box 639, Folder 3-4, Box 640, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, David - C (Box 640, Folder 2-5)
      - Rockefeller, David - D (Box 641, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, David - E (Box 641, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, David - F (Box 642, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, David - G (Box 642, Folder 4-5, Box 643, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, David - H (Box 643, Folder 2-4)
      - Rockefeller, David - I-K (Box 644, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, David - L (Box 645, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, David - M (Box 645, Folder 4, Box 646, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, David - N (Box 646, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, David - N-O (Box 647, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, David - P-Q (Box 647, Folder 2-4)
      - Rockefeller, David - R (Box 647, Folder 5, Box 648, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, David - S (Box 648, Folder 3-4, Box 649, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, David - T (Box 649, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, David - T-U (Box 649, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, David - V (Box 650, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, David - W (Box 650, Folder 2-4)
      - Rockefeller, David - X-Z (Box 651, Folder 1)
      - Addresses-Remarks - A-C (Box 651, Folder 2-5)
      - Addresses-Remarks - D-R (Box 652, Folder 1-6)
      - Addresses-Remarks - R-Z (Box 653, Folder 1-3)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Chamber of Commerce - Panama Industries and Agriculture (Box 653, Folder 4)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Chamber of Commerce - Panama Industries and Agriculture - Venezuelan-American Caracas (Box 653, Folder 5)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Institute of International Education (Box 654, Folder 1)
      - Addresses-Remarks - International House(s) (Box 654, Folder 2)
      - Addresses-Remarks - Sid W. Richardson Foundation (Box 654, Folder 3)
      - Addresses-Remarks - United Negro College Fund, 1983 March 10 (Box 654, Folder 4)
      - Articles - A-Z (Box 655, Folder 1-3)
      - Autographs (Box 656, Folder 1)
      - Awards - A-Z (Box 656, Folder 2-5)
      - Awards - MacDowell Colony (Box 657, Folder 1-2)
      - Beetles (Box 657, Folder 3)
      - Binnewies, Robert O. and Midge (Box 657, Folder 4)
      - Biography (Box 657, Folder 5)
      - 70th Birthday 1985 (Box 658, Folder 1)
      - 71st Birthday 1986 (Box 658, Folder 2)
      - Book (Box 658, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Cards, 1982-1983, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 4-6)
      - Dinner-Luncheons - A-Z (Box 659, Folder 1-3)
      - Dinner-Luncheons - Ahidjo, Ahmadou (President of Cameroon) (Box 660, Folder 1)
      - Dinner-Luncheons - Asia Society, 1983 September 22 (Box 660, Folder 2-3)
      - Dinner-Luncheons - Corporate Giving International (Box 660, Folder 4, Box 661, Folder 1)
      - Dinner-Luncheons - Receptions - Museum of Modern Art (Box 661, Folder 2)
      - Dinner-Luncheons - Yen, Dr. Jimmy (Box 661, Folder 3)
      - Gifts - A-Z (Box 661, Folder 4)
      - Giving Program (Box 661, Folder 5)
      - Interviews (Box 661, Folder 6)
      - Investments (Box 661, Folder 7)
      - Investments - Mayfield III, 1979-1980 (Box 662, Folder 1)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-F, 1982-1986 (Box 662, Folder 2-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - G-T, 1982-1986 (Box 663, Folder 1-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - U-Z, 1982-1986 (Box 664, Folder 1-2)
      - King, Hassan II (Box 664, Folder 3)
      - McBain, James A. (Box 664, Folder 4)
      - Oral History (Box 664, Folder 5)
        Scope and Contents
        David Rockefeller oral history interview conducted by Linda Edgerly, Archivist, Chase Bank, 1980-1981.
      - Photographs - A-Z (Box 665, Folder 1)
      - Political Contributions 1982-1983 (Box 665, Folder 2)
      - Political Contributions 1984 (Box 665, Folder 3)
      - Political Contributions 1985 (Box 665, Folder 4)
      - Political Contributions 1985-1986 (Box 666, Folder 1-2)
      - Property (Box 667, Folder 1)
      - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 667, Folder 2)
      - Property - St. Barts (Box 667, Folder 3)
      - Purchases (Box 666, Folder 3)
      - Radio-TV (Box 666, Folder 4)
      - Radio-TV - National Broadcasting Corporation (NBC) (Box 666, Folder 5)
      - Property - Reed, Joseph Verner, Jr. (Box 666, Folder 6)
      - Property - Reed, Joseph Verner, Jr., 1984-1986 (Box 668, Folder 1)
      - Property - Reed, Joseph Verner, Jr., 1974-1983 (Box 668, Folder 2)
      - Roosevelt, Archibald B. Jr. and Mrs. Selwa (Box 668, Folder 3)
      - David Rockefeller-Abby Rockefeller Charitable Lead Trust (Box 668, Folder 4)
      - Trips (Box 669, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Africa, 1982 (Box 669, Folder 2)
      - Trips - Asia, 1982-1983; 1986 March (Box 669, Folder 3-4)
      - Trips - France (Box 670, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Japan (Box 670, Folder 2)
      - Trips - Latin America, 1985 February (Box 670, Folder 3)
      - Trips - Middle East-South East Asia, 1984 February (Box 670, Folder 4)
      - Trips - Morocco, 1983 February (Box 670, Folder 5)
      - Trips - Mozambique-South Africa, 1984 April (Box 670, Folder 6)
      - Trips - Spain, 1986 May (Box 670, Folder 7)
      - Trips - Venezuela, 1983 January (Box 671, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Washington, DC (Box 671, Folder 2)
      - Trusts (Box 667, Folder 4)
      - Trusts - Edgell, Stephanie (Box 667, Folder 5)
      - Trusts - Edgell, Stephen M. (Box 672, Folder 1)
      - Trusts - Helena Edgell Franklin Trust (Box 672, Folder 2)
      - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 671, Folder 3-4)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - A-Z (Box 671, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 674, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Maine Coast Heritage Trust - Contributions (Box 674, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Music Assistance Fund (Box 674, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, David, Jr. (Box 672, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, David, Jr. - Addresses-Remarks (Box 672, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, David, Jr. - Chamber of Music Speech and Food Research Material, 1984 (Box 673, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, David, Jr. - Food Research (Box 673, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Diana N. - A-Z (Box 673, Folder 3)
      - Dulany, Quatrone (Box 632, Folder 4)
      - Goodwin, Neva Rockefeller (Box 632, Folder 5)
      - Growald, Mr. Paul Jeffrey and Mrs. Eileen McGrath Rockefeller (Box 632, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Abby A. (Box 638, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Abby A. - Investments - Clivus Multrum (Box 638, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Richard (Box 763, Folder 5)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Sr. (and family), 4
      - Rockefeller, John D. Sr. (Box 674, Folder 4)
      - Book - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events (Box 674, Folder 5-6, Box 675, Folder 1)
      - Book - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events - Mockup and Background Material, 1983 August (Box 675, Folder 2)
      - Book - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1983-1984 (Box 675, Folder 3-4)
      - Book - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events - Acknowledgements - A-Z (Box 676, Folder 1)
      - Book - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events - Original Magazine Articles (Box 676, Folder 2)
      - Book - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events - Christmas Gifts - LSR family, David Rockefeller family (Box 677, Folder 1)
      - John D. Rockefeller Family Cemetery Corporation (Box 676, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, John D. Sr. (Box 676, Folder 4)
      - Trusts - De Cuevas Trust, 1976-1986 (Box 677, Folder 2-3, Box 678, Folder 1-2)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (and family), 5
      - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. - A-Z (Box 676, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich - A-Z (Box 676, Folder 6)
        Including but not limited to: Bernice Kert biography.
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - A-Z (Box 676, Folder 7)
    - John D. Rockefeller, 3rd (and family), 6
      - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd. - A-Z (Box 679, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette H. (Box 679, Folder 2)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - A-Z (Box 679, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV (Jay) (Box 678, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV (Jay) - Award (Box 678, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Sharon (Box 680, Folder 1)
      - Aldrich, Hope (Box 627, Folder 2)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Giving Programs (Box 627, Folder 3)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 627, Folder 4)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Payment Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 627, Folder 5)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Payment Letters, 1983-1985 (Box 628, Folder 1)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Charitable Lead Trusts (Box 628, Folder 2)
      - Aldrich, Hope - Charitable Lead Grants - A-Z (Box 628, Folder 3-4)
      - Dayton, Mr. and Mrs. Mark Brandt and Alida Davidson Rockefeller (Box 629, Folder 6)
      - Alida and Mark Dayton Charitable Lead Trust (Box 629, Folder 7)
      - Alida and Mark Dayton Charitable Trust - Charitable Lead Trust - A-C (Box 629, Folder 8-9)
      - Alida and Mark Dayton Charitable Trust - Charitable Lead Trust - D-Z (Box 630, Folder 1-6)
      - Alida R. Dayton - Giving Program (Box 631, Folder 1)
      - Alida R. Dayton - Loans - Ms. Foundation for Education and Communications, Inc. (Box 631, Folder 2)
      - Alida R. Dayton - Red Ghost Films, LTD Partnership (Box 631, Folder 3)
      - Eric John Dayton - Charitable Lead Trust (Box 631, Folder 4)
      - Eric John Dayton - Charitable Lead Trust - A-M (Box 631, Folder 5-6)
      - Eric John Dayton - Charitable Lead Trust - N-Z (Box 632, Folder 1-3)
      - Rockefeller, Sandra (Ferry) (Box 764, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Sandra (Ferry) - Giving Programs (Box 764, Folder 3)
      - Spencer, Benjamin (Box 767, Folder 4)
      - Spencer, David (Box 767, Folder 5)
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller (and family), 7
      - Agendas (Box 679, Folder 4)
      - Articles (Box 679, Folder 5)
      - Articles - National Geographic Society (Box 681, Folder 1-2)
      - National Geographic - Calendar (Box 681, Folder 3-4)
      - Automobiles (Box 682, Folder 1)
      - Awards - A-Z (Box 682, Folder 2-3)
      - Awards - Animal Medical Center (Box 682, Folder 4)
      - Awards - Brown University (Box 682, Folder 5)
      - Awards - International Center for the Disabled (ICD) (Box 682, Folder 6)